Grandpa: Here are the fliers, hot of the press!
Ellen: Looks good. Simple.
Marilyn: Right over there, Grandpa. You fold the fliers, Richard and I will put them into the envelopes.
Richard: We finished addressing over three hundred envelopes.
Grandpa: Need another box?
Ellen: Good work, gang.
Mike: Hi, this is Mike Johnson. Can I speak with Mr. Or Mrs. Anderson? Thanks.
Robbie: Mr. Nelson. Hi. This is Robbie Stewart. Did you know my mother is running for the school board?
Jimmy: Yes, Miss Kim, Ellen Stewart.”She cares.” Oh, see you at the polls.
Robbie: Certainly, I’ll give her your best wishes, Mr. Nelson.
Mike: Hi, this is Mike Johnson. Can I speak with Mr. or Mrs. Burns? Thank you.
Ellen: We have done so much in such a short amount of time. I can’t believe it! Wait till Philip come and sees our progress!
Robbie: Everyone saw story in the Riverdale newspaper.
Ellen: Mr. Maxwell was very kind to print my announcement.
Grandpa: It helps enormously. Everybody in Riverdale reads his paper.
Richard: Your photo in it helped, too.
Ellen: Thanks to you, Richard, it’s a good picture.
Philip: Well, hi, all. Richard&Robbi e Hi, Dad.
Ellen: Hello, darling.
Philip: May I…may I help?
Marilyn: Licking envelopes.
Grandpa: I fold the fliers.
Richard: We stuff them.
Philip: And I lick the envelopes.
Robbie: Hey, everybody, Mrs. Greenberg is on the phone. She says Carter Boswell is on the TV right now-doing a commercial.
Philip: What channel?
Robbie: Five.
Philip: Five?
Boswell: …and if you ask what I care about, I’ll tell you. I care about the school buildings in need of paint. I care about more lockers for the teachers. I care about new fixtures in the hallways-not music or dancing or entertainment. I care about the practical things. If you do, vote for me, Carter Boswell.
Ellen: A lot of people will agree with him.
Philip: I told you.
Robbie: Too bad kids can’t vote. It’s our school, but we can’t vote.
Richard: There are people in favor of the cultural programs, Mom.
Marilyn: There are, Ellen. Don’t be upset by Boswell’s commercial.
Philip: You have to go on television, too.
Ellen: Boswell’s a powerful speaker.
Philip: You can be, too. Your ideas are good ones.
Ellen: I don’t know. I’m not sure I’m up to it.